<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Miguel Lopez</title>
    <link>https://KTM888.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Miguel Lopez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 14:09:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://KTM888.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Wireshark Turorial - Customising Columns and Layout for productivity</title>
      <link>https://KTM888.github.io/blog/wireshark-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 14:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KTM888.github.io/blog/wireshark-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>Intro This a tutorial of wireshark (an open-source packet analyzer) that will teach you how to customize the layout and columns of the GUI interface to optimize your productivity while learning how to navegate through it properly and effectively.
Web Traffic and the Default Wireshark Column Display Malware distribution frequently occurs through web traffic, and we also see this channel used for data exfiltration and command and control activity. Wireshark’s default column is not ideal when investigating such malware-based infection traffic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forcing Visits to use SSL</title>
      <link>https://KTM888.github.io/blog/force-ssl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 14:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://KTM888.github.io/blog/force-ssl/</guid>
      <description>Intro Doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter whether it&amp;rsquo;s a CakePHP app for a client, your own personal CMS, or any other web based application. If your passing around passwords or other sensitive info you should really implement SSL. SSL provides 2 main perks to your visitors.
 First it encrypts all communication that flies across the web. This prevents curious or devious billies from getting your secrets. Secondly it ensures to the user that your server is in fact who it claims, and not a nasty &amp;lsquo;man in the middle&amp;quot; attack.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
